[{"answer": "Hi my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend. my friend sits beside my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why d'you think I'm going now? that plac", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Hey, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "The my friend was built in nineteen twent", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yes, yes I am. The icing on the cake would be getting that landmark status from the City. We're hoping my friend can pull a few strings", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes, yes I am. The icing on the cake would be getting that landmark status from the City. We're hoping my friend can pull a few strings", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "my friend can do anything he puts his mind to. He's fine, my friend.  And you should say hello to him, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Yeah, put these glasses on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, well my friend, he's gonna be here any minute now", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "'s not necessary", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I know that, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, you know.  It's understandable. He pats my friend on the knee", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Warning signs", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": " Hey! Hey, you!  Come back here!! Don't gallop away!! my friend runs away, yelling after the retreating my friend.  my friend and my friend sit in a booth. There's a different cashier on duty", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "I'm telling you, that cashier is riding horses on my money", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Wow. Well, don't you sweat it. You can use my car any time you want to", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "No kidding", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " What is Lloyd's problem", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Uhh, I got sprayed with a hose", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "And I suppose my friend had something to do with it too", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What cashier", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " That was your best friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "That man was wearing glasses", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": " I gave you a hundred dollars?", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It's a lotta gum!  The room is festooned with props and costumes from old movies", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Well eh, we prefer to call it the Institute. my friend notices a particular costume", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Gum.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, yes, it is", "qsentId": 28}]